qmov.net 2006-06-18

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

The Information We Collect: We do not collect any customer information. Please see our payment processor's Privacy Policy concerning collected information. 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Qmov website. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name  
Address  
Zip/Town  
Email address  
Phone number  
Email

The Way We Use Information: 

We use the information gathered from our members for customer support and dispute resolution. Your information will never be sold to a third-party by Proximus Media Inc.

Our Commitment To Data Security 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information: 

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by visiting the website of the payment processor that you signed up with. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

How To Contact Us: 

Proximus Media, Inc.   
1155 W. 4th Street, Suite 214   
Reno, NV 89503

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us [here](http://www.happymember.com/)
